{
  "title": "Essential Japanese Expressions Quiz II",
  "description": "Expand your proficiency in Japanese with a diverse set of essential phrases and expressions.",
    "items": [
      {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "How do you say 'I don't know' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "Shirimasen",
        "options": ["Hai", "Iie", "Shirimasen", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Expressing lack of knowledge"
      },
      {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'Hot' (temperature)?",
        "answer": "Atsui",
        "options": ["Atsui", "Iie", "Konnichiwa", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Describing warm or hot weather"
      },
      {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "How do you ask 'What is your name?' in a formal way?",
        "answer": "O-namae wa nan desu ka",
        "options": ["Anata wa dare desu ka", "Kore wa nan desu ka", "O-namae wa nan desu ka", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Formally inquiring about someone's name"
      },
      {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'Big'?",
        "answer": "Ookii",
        "options": ["Ookii", "Chisai", "Konnichiwa", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Describing something as large or big"
      },
      {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "How do you say 'I'm thirsty' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "Nodo ga kawakimashita",
        "options": ["Nodo ga kawakimashita", "Iie", "Konnichiwa", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Expressing thirst"
      },
      {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'Happy'?",
        "answer": "Ureshii",
        "options": ["Wakarimasen", "Iie", "Ureshii", "Wakarimasu"],
        "hint": "Expressing joy or happiness"
      },
      {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "How do you ask 'What is this?' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "Kore wa nan desu ka",
        "options": ["Anata wa nani desu ka", "Kore wa nan desu ka", "Ima nan-ji desu ka", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Inquiring about an object"
      },
      {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'Fast'?",
        "answer": "Hayai",
        "options": ["Konnichiwa", "Hayai", "Sayonara", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Describing quick or fast movement"
      },
      {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "How do you say 'Good afternoon' in Japanese?",
        "answer": "Konnichiwa",
        "options": ["Ohayou gozaimasu", "Konbanwa", "Konnichiwa", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Afternoon greeting"
      },
      {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "What is the Japanese word for 'Slow'?",
        "answer": "Osoi",
        "options": ["Osoi", "Iie", "Konnichiwa", "Arigatou"],
        "hint": "Describing slow or leisurely movement"
      }
    ]
  }
  